The next day
Shobonetto, Shobonetto, the dreamy
Shobonetto
Wow, everyone, it looks so delicious!
I'm so happy!
It's been a while!
You look so energetic!
I'm so energetic!
Today, I have something to tell you!
I brought something special for you!
I've never seen anything like this
before.
This is the best!
The previous product was also very
popular.
I'm sure you'll buy it this time as
well.
Who is it?
I'm the president of GAL-TOO-HAN.
I'm so happy!
I'll introduce the product.
It's a good news!
Minari and Fan Club is the official fan
club of Minari and Aoki.
If you register as a member, you can
enjoy the original web content exclusive
to members.
Yay!
First, please introduce yourself to the
president of Minari and Aoki.
Let me introduce myself!
First, I'm Minari, a digital member.
And I'm a ticket-preferred recipient of
Minari!
And then, behind Kirari, there's a
member chat!
What's that? Behind?
And then, behind Kirari, there's a
member content!
group chat!
And then, there's more?
There's more!
I can't remember all of it!
And then, there's a group chat!
And then, a sudden Q&A time!
What? Q&A time?
And then, a Q&A time with me!
And then, an e-mail magazine!
And then, a birthday...
And then, a Q&A time with me!
I can't remember because it's too
heavy!
I was so excited!
Thank you so much!
Everyone, you were really interested in
the introduction of the new product,
right?
Right?
So let's introduce each one of them!
Introduction of the new product
First, I would like to explain the
digital member!
If you join the E-NIGHT FUNK CLUB,
you can get a digital membership!
The first one is the membership card.
Yes, it is.
You can get the membership card with
your face on it.
You can also choose the postcard.
I'm so happy.
The membership card is important.
You can get the certificate of the fan
club.
I'm not good at English.
You can get the card as a proof.
Please get the card.
Next, we will introduce the ticket.
We will tell you how to get our ticket
at Minion and Fan Club.
Really?
Then, I might be the first one!
That's right!
Yay!
Everyone wants to be the first one,
right?
So, we want to go to the live!
Please join us to get this ticket and
the first-come-first-served!
Please!
And then, next is...
What?
Here it is!
You guys are curious, right?
This is...
Meba Chako!
This is a talk room for members who
can't see each other here.
We might be able to hear everyone's
secret stories here.
Let's post it here now.
Oh, I see.
Let's do it.
Let's post it right away.
What kind of post would you like to
post?
I don't know what to post.
The president just posted it.
He posted it.
He said, I'm Tachimana from Chobonet.
The president sent it to me.
I'll post it now.
Wow, it's here.
I just posted it.
I'm excited.
You can feel our daily lives here.
If you want to hear our secret stories,
please come and see us.
Please subscribe to our channel.
The next main event is...
Member contents!
Members are updating their contents on
a daily basis.
Each member has a different content.
For example, Karei Tachibana's...
Karei's health session.
Hikaru's secret...
And Kitani's...
Let's do it again!
Yasumori Waka's...
Yasumori's famous.
And Kichise Shinju's...
Shinju's left shoulder.
And Takuya Hinano's...
Hinano's fantasy diary.
Fujitani's...
Lucky Fujitani's happy entertainment.
And Date's...
Date's illustration.
And Hazuki's growth record.
We have a lot of contents that you are
curious about.
Let's show you our contents.
We'll show you what we actually write.
We'll write our diary and growth
record.
This is the product.
Ta-da!
We are collaborating with this.
Salted chocolate cookie bread.
Let's eat.
It's sweet.
It smells good.
There are chocolate chips.
It's good.
It's sweet.
I think it's 5 out of 10.
It's pretty sweet.
It's good.
It's fluffy.
The top is cookie dough, so it's
crispy.
I like the texture.
I eat like this.
I write a diary like this.
I upload by e-mail from time to time.
Hello everyone!
Today's caren aka.
A healthy conversation.
Watch every year on TV.
come out like flesh and blood
Cute!
Yes.
So, it was a time to get healthy with
Tachibana Kamen.
How was it, everyone?
Did you feel better?
I was very satisfied.
Let's do our best together from
tomorrow!
Bye bye!
So, how is the member content updated?
I would like you to join the public
display here.
I introduced Financier the other day.
Financier!
I'll show you my stomach, so please
come and see it.
That was the member content.
Next is the limited movie!
Loving movie!
...so here you go
We'll settle our tone
Okay, limited movie has broadcast a
number of live performances, backstage
interviews,
videotapes of entertainment and
messages to the audience!
And this one...
was also uploaded as new as of late
We've collected all the photos we took.
Yes.
Next,
the first-ever, quote-unquote,
live-action confession scene.
It was amazing, wasn't it?
It was.
It's a monthly release.
And the birthday message.
And the analysis.
We've looked into all of them.
And more, and more, and more.
We're releasing them.
Wow.
It's amazing, isn't it?
We're doing YouTube like this,
and we're releasing a movie that only
we can watch.
So you can get to know us better.
Don't you want to see it?
I do.
Because movies are so charming.
That's right.
I usually wear a cap,
so you can't see me here.
Okay.
Do you get it?
Yes.
Yes, yes, yes.
That's how it is.
So, tomorrow,
we're going to have a movie.
Off-shot gallery event.
We had a movie earlier,
a movie,
but you can see the photos, too.
Really?
We're going to have a live show and an
event.
We're going to show you the photos.
So,
look forward to it.
Yes.
And, and, and,
we saw it.
Asking Us Anything, BYE!
Rich Girl No.1
You got used to the prank…?
The members will answer your questions.
We are excited every time.
We get your answers, not your names.
We can feel your feelings.
That's right.
It's good.
Everyone asks questions.
We are going to answer them.
Don't you want to be answered?
We want to be answered.
Yeah!
Please send us a lot of questions.
We are ready to answer.
Next is wallpapers.
Wallpapers.
We have uploaded wallpapers.
Really?
I didn't know that.
What kind of wallpapers?
You don't know.
We have uploaded a lot.
It's gorgeous.
Please show us your wallpapers.
It's time for Mail Mahochin!
We have the latest information in our
mail magazine.
Please check it out.
Sign.
Next is the birthday mail.
As you can see, we have a message movie
from the fan.
Wow, amazing!
Isn't it crazy?
The best happiness is to celebrate your
birthday with your favorite person.
I can't do it.
Happy birthday, Karen!
Please subscribe to my channel!
You can celebrate your favorite event
once a year.
It's a special event.
You want it, don't you?
Yes, I do.
Let's get in.
Please select the music and dance songs
I sang in this video!
I think the most important thing is the
goods.
That's right.
This is a serious matter.
I agree.
Is gyaru important?
Yes, gyaru is important.
But, all the goods I introduced so far
are...
What?
The price is...
500 yen!
And if you continue to be a member of
the Inari Tohoku Fan Club for a year,
you will receive a membership card!
Maybe, someday, if you have a
membership card, there may be something.
Maybe not.
Maybe!
Maybe there is!
It's so special!
It's so luxurious!
Thank you!
So, did you get interested in the
membership card?
Of course!
The application has already started!
Please check the description of this
video for more details!
Thank you for watching today's video!
Thank you!
You did a great job today, too!
You did a great job, too!
Thank you!
I'll keep doing my best!
Have a nice day!